I might cry so hard when I see these three outfits and hear the dance "The Future is Here.
I know, right?
The face is like this, while the face that there is every day becomes...
Yes, people might feel the darkness.
Yesterday's dance, the truth of the testimony.
That's how we prove our existence.
Good morning.
We're going to start part of the show after this, but...
We have Kyo-san here with us today.
Oh, wow! That letter!
We made you laugh on Twitter, and you were both in Cabbage Taro's eyes.
It came for a year, didn't it?
Yes, a year's worth.
We received this for a year.
Thank you, Mr. President of Cabbage Taro.
It has a message attached, so thank you for purchasing Cabbage Taro.
I Cabbage, using high quality corn and
He said it is a lighter snack food with more palatability to the toasted seasoning.
I'm glad to hear that regardless of the communication network.
I got your message, too.
I hope you'll all try them.
They are delicious.
I really hope that Kyo-san will join us next time at a live concert or something.
What should I do if I see him?
Please take care of the president of Cabbage Taro, everyone.
Please do.
We have a lot of snacks, so if we do one at a time, we might be able to get at least one for Kyo-san.
You eat too much.
I like these snacks, so please work with the president of these snacks.
I have some here too.
Do you think the president will see it?
Wachubo.
I'm looking forward to working with any of these presidents.
Please.
Hey, I like this one.
I absolutely hate this.
Please give my regards to the presidents of the Novell man name sheet here.
Gentlemen, how are you?
We're having a reading event today.
You can win this.
Ladies and gentlemen, I'd like to have lunch for you.
Today, this way.
Good night.
Let's go.
Today, right? This way! You can tell from the kanji...
Shumai... vent?
Huh? This? I don't know the ratio.
I want to try the shumai bento!
I'm off!
Oh!
Surprise!
Thank you for your hard work!
That's amazing. You did it out of the blue.
You said you were filming something.
I was wondering if it was true, sorry.
Bye bye, bye, bye!
We're being filmed!
Scary!
It's over, Yumeto and I.
It was so much fun!
It's always so hard to change out of all the costumes
It's a lot of work, but it's fun to change my hair every time.
It's fun to change my hair every time.
It's been a long time since I've been to a member's meeting.
It's been so long since I've been to a member's meeting.
I love Hana-sama! Thank you so much!
Is today's work finished?
Yes, I'm done!
Thank you very much!
Bye-bye!
Good morning.
It's Ichimuchi here, rehearsing for the band rehearsal for Mishinarika's birthday live.
I'm so nervous. My stomach hurts.
We are now in rehearsal.
I will do my best.
Please do your best.
I did my best. I was nervous.
What kind of live show is it going to be?
Eh.
I think we're doing our best.
How are the members?
They were really nice.
They all said they were good at what they were doing, but they came back saying they would do their best.
I thought, "If I don't do my best, I won't be able to do my best.
Yes, I'll do my best.
Good morning.
Today's coordination is here.
Here are the coordinates for the first day of this year!
By all means, please.
What are those? What are those gummy bears?
No, they're pure gummy bears.
Wow.
Yay.
There you go. We're trading gummy bears.
What day is it today?What day is it today?
What day?
Friday
Today's Sweets Friday.
That's right.
It's Gummi Day.
I've got a lot of work to do, so I'll do my best.
It's important. I'm kind of dressed to move around today.
Laughs
♪ Music
Thank you.
♪ From me among the singers to the front
Yes, sir.
Can you do it?
# Forward from me, the one who sings
Practice in song.
How was it?
Harder than I thought it would be.
I'm dancing pretty well.
I'll do my best.
There are only five days left until the show.
I haven't sung at all today.
I'll do my best.
The unveiling is over.
I'm off to rehearsal now
I'm off to rehearsal.
Good afternoon.
Today we're going to try our hand at biohazard.
I've done it twice before. I've done it twice before.
Recently...
You're good at biohazard, aren't you?
I'm getting better!
If you've seen the last two times...
I'm sure you can tell.
I did it a while ago.
I was so scared.
I don't know, it just wasn't for me.
If it wasn't horror, I could do it.
I can handle gore.
Please listen to this Resident Evil.
If it's not horror, I can do it.
Resident Evil has a little horror in it.
Yes, a little.
I just want to make an excuse that I might not be able to do it.
We'll resume the game where we left off.
You have a bug in your hand.
What? What? What?
Huh?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You scared me.
I think that's all for now.
It's almost 10:00.
Go to bed early, all right?
That's all for now.
This was an Ultracar limited broadcast.
See you soon.
Bye bye.
I don't know what I would do if I did it
The distribution is over.
Thank you all for watching.
I hope you enjoyed it.
With the members, yeah.
I don't know if I'd do that if I did it every time.
I'd like to have a chance to do it with the members sometimes.
I think I've been doing it a lot.
Everyone is.
I think they have a lot of fun playing together.
It makes the show a lot of fun.
As a game lover.
I like Open Neck a lot.
I'm going to be playing a lot of fun games in the future.
I hope you guys check it out.
Bye, bye, bye.
Bye bye bye, I'm going home.
Here are today's groups
Turtles
This is my favorite series right now, Turtles!
I look forward to working with you.
Thank you for dinner.
Hello.
Good evening.
Good afternoon.
Since we're looking back today.
I will be polite and serious.
The venue wasn't bad, so I had you look back.
I'm sorry if I made you all wait.
Let's do our best to be polite.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Thank you for your patience.
Thank you for waiting.
I was hmmm... I had to choose one face or the other.
I had two, so I came before.
Thank you for waiting.
I've been here before.
I'm going to turn around and blur.
Okay, I'm leaving.
Bye bye, Natsu.Bye bye, Natsu.
I'll see you later.
I was silent from the polite voice.
See you later.
Oh no, what's that?
Cabbage taro, what is it?
Squeaky.
I'm good at this.
I'm good.
It's about time I share it with everyone.
I can't do it today.
You can't come in?
No, I can't. Please take it.
I'll bring it tomorrow.
We're done.
Good morning.
I have received
I received a bag of camelstraw.
I'll take it home with me.
You're doing a great job today.
Rika, you're so particular.
What? You're taking pictures while you're home?
That's so cute.
I'm going to play that the manager was very close to me the whole time I was there.
Well, that's it for today.
I'll have a Cabbage Taro and a Frappuccino, and then I'll be on my way.
Thank you for your hard work.
Here it comes!
Okay, let's go!
How do you want it?
Vertical.
Vertical, yeah.
I'll make it.
Here we go.
That's unusual, today.
Really?
You don't seem very interested.
Here you go. Cheese.
I don't see any cherries.
Tulip.
You can't see most of them.
Here you go. Cheese.
Thank you for your hard work.
Are you finished for the day?
Yes, I'm done.
I'm always nervous when you ask me that.
I thought there might be something there.
I'm done.
Well then, thank you for your hard work.
What is this video?
Thank you for your hard work.
Good morning.
Today is the online talk session.
We have 5 minutes left, but Wada-chan was so quiet that she didn't speak a single word just now.
I'll practice my vocalization?
I'll do my best with a pacifier combo for today's offering.
Food semi.
Please.
Please do your best.
Thank you.
Fun, fun.
I'm done.
I don't know, you made me go around a lot more than I thought I would.
And I got in trouble.
Well, that's okay.
The person who hit it didn't do anything serious.
It's private damage.
Please don't do that.
Private damage?
Yes, totally.
Damage to privacy...
Damage to privacy.
Please don't do that.
Why are you laughing?
Tell me again.
Let me say it one more time.
Invasion of privacy.
I'm afraid I've done some damage...
I don't know if this is coming.
Good morning.
Invasion of privacy.
Camera shake.
How are you guys really doing?
It's an invasion, isn't it?
What are you going to do now?
Damage.
Damage now.
Damage to the private life of the film.
I'm afraid.
Everyone has quizzes on their wall.
I'll be waiting for you at the reception.
Please come this way.
This is a strawberry chocolate!
Thank you very much.
It's over!It's over!
How many days to go until the live show for decades?
Tens of days!
But is this the first time you've rehearsed for the 10,000th anniversary live concert in Japan? It was the first time we went through it today.
It was my first time to go through the rehearsal, so I could see the future. Enjoy!
I'll do my best!
Good morning.
Doesn't it seem awfully early in the morning?
Indeed. A smile makes all the difference.
Indeed.
I was here until midnight yesterday, and I'm working hard from this morning again today.
I've been surprisingly busy.
What will you be doing today?
Well, I heard that we are going to perform a new song tomorrow.
I didn't know.
It's not tomorrow. The day after tomorrow.
The day after tomorrow.
Tomorrow's show will be confirmation and new songs.
We'll do it.
I'm appealing for a long story.
We always perform at this distance.
I'll go a little closer to the foundation.
No, no, no. This is the best distance.
I didn't know.
I'm one with the dilusions and the image, so I'll do my best!
I am going to go to my singing lesson today.
Have a good day.
Today I am going to have a vocal lesson now.
I'm going to do some new songs.
I'm off.
What? That's not fair!
What? What is it? Who are you?
He said he finished his lesson early.
Singing lesson is over.
Did you work hard? I did.
You worked hard.
Look.
Take a look.
There's nothing to look at. Nothing.
Goodbye.
Stop it.
Stop filming.
What's going to happen now?
What's going on?
I'm going to go have some tea.
I'm going to go to a place with such a great sound.
I'm off to a lesson.
Good luck with your lesson.
I'll do my best.
Batantan, over there.
Orange apple.
I'm lost.
Let's go.
Who's the best?
I want a drink. I'm ready.
I'll go. Se-no.
Stop it.
Reverses!
I'm going!
I love it.
That's amazing.
I didn't know that was possible.
Let's go for second choice.
No, no, no, no.
Let's go without peaches.
If it's peaches, just peaches.
Okay.
Ready?
Eeeee...
Wow!
That's great!
You want some of that?
I'll take it! I'll take it!
Wow!
We all wore the same thing the first time.
Then I said, "Let's definitely pick a candidate.
We all split up.
No!
Definitely, Momo!
She was stubborn.
Some people are hard to see.
It's hard to see.
I wanted it to fit perfectly.
This is great.
Bon appétit.
Cheers!
We're on a roll.
I wish I could have had a Momo.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors. One round.
No, no, no! No, no, no, no, no!
Ten minutes ago.
It's rustling.
Hey, it's close.
I don't even know if it's a costume.
I'm scared.That's scary.
You don't even know if it's a costume.
No, I can't polidge down anymore.
I can't...
I was already here.
I'll do my best.
Please.
Shun!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Huh?
I'd like to see the other members, don't you, guys?
Just for a moment, then.
It can't be helped.
Waste of time.
Excuse me for a moment.
Shun!
Yes, you're here already.
I'll do my best.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you for your time.
Okashi-toko.
Kankankankankankankankankankankankankankankankankankankankankankankankankan.
It was fun. It's been kind of a long time.
I like Oist.
So it was fun.
Hey, you like Oist, don't you? Really.
That's the exact same comment.
I didn't make such a decision, but I did it sitting in a chair or standing up.
Hey and like...oh, that's what you mean? That's what you mean by not deciding.
You like to be with them, don't you? From the audience's point of view...oh, personally. The venue...well, the venue...you know.
The venue...well, I did my best.
Good morning.
What are you doing now?
I'm going on the radio now.
I have a meeting first.
A meeting.
Matsuda, you're late.
Yes, I'll expose your tardiness.
This is the second or third time in five rounds.
Matsuda-chan, please.
Never be late!
Absolutely no tardiness.
Then, please.
I'll do my best.
Next.
Wiccan time.
How'd you drink till morning?
There's a lot of people.
A lot.
Grapes.
This is from yesterday's show and in the dressing room.
And oranges.
they both brought them today.
I had to take them home, but once I did...
brought them again.
They're delicious.
You didn't eat it.
It's delicious.
Hello? Hello? Hello?
Thank God you're okay.
Would you two like to introduce yourselves?
Delicious.
Yes, we are The World Standard.
Stand!
We are Nanase Hirokawa and Maimi Matsuda. Pleased to meet you.
It's over.
It was fun, wasn't it?
It was fun.
We laughed a lot.
I thought the sense of the messages that the worshipers sent to the radio
I thought the sense of the messages that the worshipers sent to the radio was very nice.
They were all different from each other.
I think they are all different from each other, and they are all a little bit habitual, rather than doing this or that.
I'm sorry.
I was entertained.
It was fun.
After this, I have a news event in the evening.
I'll do my best.
I'll do my best after all.
The guests are coming in now.
They are coming in and starting.
They are entering.
I'm going to go.
I want to be the name
Lukomi's.
Tonight, together, together, we've been looking to the future.
So, today is the release date.
This single is the first single after the new organization.
You've done a lot of release events, haven't you?
Yes, we have.
So I feel like it's finally here.
But there might be people who are seeing the release event live for the first time today.But there may be people who are seeing the release event live for the first time today.
I hope you enjoy the event.
Always a drama of love
And like goodbye
Skin hits, heart flies, crosses over to courage
Now I have to tell you who I'm talking about
You've got to take it in
Do it with my feminine truth
And prove it
Musical Dance has been released!
I've released it!
I'm living on so much grass.
It was grass, wasn't it?
I thought it was pretty tiring to be so aware of the camera all the time.
No, no, it wasn't that much.
I guess we showed the back side of our faces.
They could tell which side was more beautiful.
That's pretty much it.
I hope you can feel the growth.
If I could feel it.
That would be nice.
That is Miraival Dance.
That's why we released Miraival Dance.
Thank you for all your support!
Thank you very much!
Please let me know when there is another close contact.
If there is a close contact, I hope it will be a good quality close contact.
Because it's a very close contact.
We are pleased to announce the Miraival Dance Oricon Daily Chart!
Great success!
I've forced myself to do it.
Great!
What a surprise!
4th place!
I'm going to change the choreography here from today.
I'll change it!
Thank you very much.
I'm so happy! Thank you very much.
You've got a nice singing voice.
I'm glad.
It's really high, but not as high as I expected.
The ranking.
I'm happy.
I'm so happy.
Thank you very much.
I want to write for everyone.
Listen to it a lot.
Listen a lot.
Bye bye.
Thank you very much.
Are you done for the day?
Yes, I'm done.
Thank you for your hard work.